But I am showing Tuba to the doctor.
Tuba's health is getting a little worse,
guys.  So now we are taking him to the hospital.
Will you apply it to me?
Yes sir.   When
children get hurt, the
parents' hearts ache.
My dear mother.
Hello everyone, how are you all?  Welcome back
to our new blog.  So guys, from today I am going to
show you the children's studies.  Because
children do not study daily.  What do you study
?  How far has the children's syllabus
reached?  You will see everything in this blog.
Good morning Zeid.
Good morning mom.
How are you?   I am
fine.
What are you doing in your studies today?
Colouring.
Zed B for
Bag.
Who are you coloring?   To the
bag.
Hold the J color well.  How do you
hold a pencil?  very good.  Hold
it properly.  Let us go.   Yes.
Okay tell me which color is this?
Yellow color.
very good.  Now tell me this?
Green color.
No this one.  This one?
Black color.   Okay now this one
?  Tell me tell me tell me tell
me
hi
no green green
good morning Ayan
good morning mummy
how are you I am fine aau
what colour is this very good
and this one
purple blue
no pink pink
and purple yes so
guys the children have learnt numbers
from one to 20 so now I will show you
what all the children have learnt so one theirs is
complete second second theirs is complete.  The
third one is also complete.
So today the children will trace four.
So Guys is tracing Na Ayan Four here.
So Ayan traced everything.
Only two are left, Ayan.  Trace it well.
Look guys, I have painted the bed.
How to do it?
Show it very well.  So guys you have to comment and
tell me how Zed colored it.  So
Guys Zad's coloring is done.  So now it's
Ayan's turn.  I asked Ayan
which one he would colour?  So he is saying, Mom,
I will do it as per my wish.  So Ayan has chosen
Robot picture.  What happened Zad?
Mummy is not a robot.  The human becomes a
robot.   He is
not a good brother.  Have you seen it happen?   Have
you ever seen a robot?
Yes, I have seen it.
How is that?
He was a robot first and then changed the loop.   The
robot had changed the loop.  Okay Ayan,
see, mom taught you by colouring.
In this we will do yellow in its face.  Here is the yellow
color.  Ayan, hold on tight.  Hold
the color properly.  Very good like a pencil.
Now Color This.  Now it's Zad's turn.
Zad will tell the alphabets.  Ok?
Ok.
A for
Apple.
B for
ball.
C for
Topsy.
No C for
Cat.
very good.  D for
Dog.
E for
Elephant.
F for
she was dead, right?
Yes, F for
your favorite?
Se G for
Gun
H for
I for
J for K for L
for
L for which row does
L for C the picture
loyal
that now we will do counting ok what happened
Anu it is done
oh Anu you have done it very beautifully you have done the same colour in all of them
you have made the entire robot
yellow yes
yellow is your favourite colour
so guys children know A to Z completely but the
recognition is only till M.
So in a few days the children will
learn more.  So right now we're doing
numbers.  Come on, tell me the counting.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 13 14 17 9
Very good very nice.  So guys ma'am is saying
that today Zadd has said till 20 for the first time.
Otherwise I would have said it by 12.  Very
good Zack clap for you clap for yourself
this is what
we are going to do now body parts Zack where
is your eyes nose lips ears teeth chin very
good show me your hands
where is your head very good and now tell me
where is your face very good where is your chest very good
where is your stomach.
Very nice fingers thumb very good legs
this this is like it is like
subscribe to the channel so
guys now Ayan has come to tell you everything
Ayan you will win
yes mumma
sure
mumma you will
not make much noise at all now Ayan
is studying ok ok don't
disturb my son A for
apple
B for
boy
C for
cat D
for
dog
E for
elephant
F for good very
good H for
hand
I for
J for
dog K
for
l for
hat Lyan Lyan what
you are doing from behind this is wrong na this
is wrong na wrong don't disturb him
Ayan now we will do counting ok come one
two tell mumma one hum two hum two very good two very good
next [laughs] Ayan
Ayan one two three four tell me like this one two three
4 5 6 7 8 9 11
next
13 14
very good you will not improve you will not
improve you with brownie  You are getting me cheated, right
?
Yes.   Isn't it
wrong?
So guys next we're doing body
parts which Zad did.  We will repeat the same.
Okay Ayan, can I ask you something?
Yes.
Where are your eyes?  Eyes.
Where are your eyes?
Eyes.
Okay very good.  So Guys, that's exactly what you
said.  Look at the picture.  These eyes.
Ok.  Where is the noose?
Nose these.
No son, no.  So guys ma'am is telling that Anu
knowingly speaks wrong.
Everything comes.  Okay Anu listen.  Look at mom here.
Where is your nose?
I don't know.  Nose nose no no
come nose Anu there is
no nose how do you sneeze ok when you
sneeze do you use your hands
no
how do you use them oh very good eyes very good nose very good
nose teeth teeth teeth very
good fingers very good ok
where is your stomach show me your small stomach where is
this stomach ok where is your thumb
light
ok and where is your hairs beautiful?
Show me how to shake your hair.  very good.  So right now
we're doing Big Small.  Okay Ayan,
tell me one thing.  Is Brownie Big or is Ayan Big?
Ok.  What is a brownie?
Small
Small.
So guys, right now we are learning the opposite.
Is Jack Ship Big or Small?
Big.
And is it small or big?
Small.
Ok.  Is the tea hot or cold?
Cold.
Mom, can I ask you something?
Yes sir.  Ask.  Mom, this is the tone.  It is tight.
Yes, you are right.  This is walnut.  This is hard.
And what is this cotton candy
?
Very good Ayan.  very good.  Keep it up.  Ayan,
tell me one thing, which one of these is old?
Which one is new?
This is old.
Yes.
This is new.
Very good Ayan.  I love it.  Zd.  Now
tell me one thing.  Which one is the weight?  Which one is dry?
This is this weight.  She has come here.
very good.  Tell me open close.  Is it open or
close?
No open close tell me again.
This is open and close.
Very good Z.  very good.  Ayan, tell me one thing, is
mom happy or sad?
Sad.
Now is mom happy or sad?
Happy.
very good.  And tell me one thing, is garbage dirty
or clean?   Is it
dirty or clean?
Dirty.
very good.  Dirty.  Come on, children, stand up.
Now we will do animals.  So guys, our
wall is so colourful.  There are many
animals in it.  So I
will ask both of them one by one.  Zad who is this?
Monkey.
Who is this your favorite?
very good.  And who is this?
Lyon.
Who is this?  Qty Payasa?
Ok.
I was on the farm, right?
Yes.  Who is this?  Do you know its name?   Did
you tell me?
Who is this?  Having a long neck.
Mujra.  Ok.  And who is this?  Motu-motu
sa
efent.
And who is this?
Hippo.
Hippopotamus.
Yes.
And who is this?  The one who has a small baby
in his pouch who runs very fast.
His name starting with K is Kangaroo.
And which character is this?
My friend.
what is your friend's name?
Doraemon.
Ok.  Ayan, who is this?  Cute?
Tiger.
Tell me the days of the week and then you will be on leave.
Ok.  Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Friday, Thursday.   Thursday
comes after Wednesday.  What comes
?
Thursday.
And whose day is Tuesday?
Of Hanuman ji.
very good.  Friend, recite your favorite poem to
all the guys.
G ate the banana, threw it in his face, went down.   Further ahead.
Threw away the peel, burned the foot, came out of the mouth.
Hi Yum.
very good.  Clapping.  Grandfather, please
recite your favourite English poem.  It's time for chhamm chhamm chhamm,
no, it's time for chubby chicks, it's time for chhamm chhamm chhamm, we went out with our umbrella,
we fell down, we're going up and down,
this is enough in Hindi, very good, now
tell me in English, chubby chicks,
chubby chicks, it's like aa
la tu t
u, yes yes yes, very
good.
In the washroom.
Okay, when you have to go to the washroom,
what do you say to madam?  May I go to the
washroom?
In the washroom.   May I go
to the washroom?
to the washroom?  So guys,
when did this child go out after completing his studies?  Anu you will get trapped.
So guys, today I am thinking that I should bring all the
things that are not there for the children.
Like
son, one minute, one minute I will come, like
come, one minute Babu, did you say something to
me, right? Guys, I do
n't know where are you taking me, what is this?
Tell me, right? Come on,
my father, come on, my Pappu, come on, come on,
now tell me,
where are you going?
Look,
what have you made for me,
dear mother,
dear mother, you have made this, dear mother, my
dear mother, you are warding off the evil
eye from me,
you have done this work, guys, this boy
is really Krishna, Krishna, oh,
where did you get the complete white colour from? Yes, as you were
told, oh
God, what should I do with it, what should I do, guys,
see, the whole father has come, will
father say, what have you transformed the house,
didi, when you were there, when the children were small,
you were the youngest, you were six days old, how the house used to shine,
yes, it looked so nice,
now see,
you have cleaned up the house, guys, there will be no
place where there are no colours, I have
kept them.  There was no space left.  Yes
son.
Mama.
Yes.   I will get
everyone's house painted by one painter.  The painter will
paint everyone's house.  Yes, okay.   I
am a painter.  I am a
painter.  You know everyone missed you a lot today.
Why?
You were not there in the entire vlog.  So all the
people here have showered a lot of love on you.
Tell me.  Thank you.   Thank
you.
You will get well soon.
What is there to see?   Should
I see?
Yes.  So guys, my daughter has been hurt so badly
but she is so brave.  She
is so brave.  Do you know if any
other child was in your place, he would have cried so much but you did
not cry, right?  Where do you get so much power from
?  Tuba, God has given me
so much power,
Mom, what is there to see in it?
Guys, there's a cute unicorn
lipstick inside.  Who ordered this
for you?
You.   Should I apply it to
you?
Look, mom.   Should I apply it to
Yes.  So guys, this is a cute little
lipstick.  Today I applied it two-three times and only then I felt
happy.  Let us look at the fragrance,
how is the fragrance?
This is also very good.
So brother, please
apply it like this, I am very cute.
Okay, should I apply it like this also?
Ok.  Suba, I don't have a towel.
What shall I do?
This is a towel.
So guys, today his father neither gave him such a lovely
towel nor did he even buy it.  No.  This is my little
doll's tow.  I will apply it only when you get it done by the barber.
Ok?  You should not take bath tomorrow also.
I will sponge you.
I will tell you on ok.
Yes, but I will tell you.  What is its name
?
very good.  Can you tell me what is this called in Hindi
Peacock.
What does Jaida call it?
Green.
What is Haredi?  See what it is called
?   Don't know.
This is the eagle.
Eagle.
What is this?
Owl.
Owl?
Which owl?  Did you call me a fool?
No.  You called me a fool.
Owl.
I owl?
Yes.
You see.  You see.
Owl.
So guys, look what a
cute washing machine Na Tuba has here.  Run it.  Look,
all the clothes are being washed.
Where are the clothes?
Kaple is inside it.  This machine does not open,
Tuba.  They just drive it like this.  The sound comes
but it does not open.  You are
opening up.   It is
not opening son.
Open up.
Shona Kaka, it is not opening.  It is not opening.
Open it from here, mom.   So that's what
I'm trying to do here.  But
this machine is not opening at all.  It just
works like this.
Please open it, mom.
My daughter Sonika doesn't open up.
Open it in your hand.
My son, should I try it in front of you?   Should I do it
again?  This is the machine.  We
started this.  Ok, I closed it from here.  Look
how much effort Mama put in.  Look look.
Look, this is not opening, you boo.  This machine is
such a showpiece.  This open blue.
Son, don't open your gold.
Mom, should I open it?  Please don't talk like this.
I feel bad.  Please don't say anything.   It is
not opening my son.   Let me open it.
Wow wow this is so beautiful.  Ishmita
Tuba will see her face, should I show her?  So guys,
here Tuba is insisting that
mom please remove my bandage.  I am feeling very hot.
So I am explaining that
if you remove the bandage then you will feel pain again.
Because guys, he was in
so much pain that you can't even imagine.
Touch wood, ever since I applied the bandage, there is
no pain like this.  Yes, I played the game.
Ok.  Ma'am, please tell me everything.
Ok?  Look at this.  You know
who this is.  Isn't it?  Ok.  Who is this?
very good.  And tell me what is its name?  Tell me, tell
me.   Don't know.
Austridge, say Austridge.   Come on, let's make
both of them fight.
Chi,
come, come, come.  Let's see who wins.  I
will win.
One to me oh [ __ ].  I: Yes,
mom, why is the poor guy not standing up?
So guys, he has made these three people stand up.  Show me this.
Put it again.  OoO it
fell again.
Mom,
yes
idea,
what idea?
What is this you are doing?  What is this you are doing?   Sit down.   Setting
Ostridge over Peacock.
Guys, that's why it wasn't getting erect.   Hey,
what's the matter, friend?  Guys OA left.   It was
arranged so beautifully.  So guys, see
how beautifully Zad has set it up.  Zada
Tooba Na is very sad.  How do we make him happy?
I have some ideas.
What's the idea?   If
you start writing, you will be happy.
Tuba may not give it.  You see what brother is doing
for you?  What happened Tuba?  Why are you
angry?  Please tell me.
My daughter, my love.  Apply lip boost first.
Yes.  Ok.  Have put.  Now let the mirror do one thing for
you.  Should I check the mirror?
Ma'am, now look in the mirror.   The
glass has survived.  [laughter]
You didn't like it, ma'am?
Okay, tell me one thing, will you listen to me?
Please listen.   Are you
my daughter?  I took care of you.  Now
neither the bandage is there nor the bandage, remove the thought of it from your heart.
I will tell the doctor tomorrow and get your
bandage removed.  Ok.
Mama.
Yes sir.
How to
make this the heart?
Yes.   The one
who has cleansed my heart Guys, don't do this dirty
child now I will
make it again for my daughter This is my daughter
's heart I love you
twice
Rani [screaming]
my heart,
my heart, you have cleansed my heart
again I
love
you
Malik
Dil
[screaming] hai dil
call me again I
won't do class call me again for sure
I won't make it I have lost I will
not make it for the
last time I have not made it
I have lost
make it for the last time for sure Tuba
is ready for you for sure Guys ever since
Tuba got hurt I
am with Tuba for 24 hours, count it 24 hours, she is
not leaving this girl for even a second She
slept for two hours, Payal and I did
not sleep even then, we were just taking care of her I
told her nothing should happen to her, she is the same guy, even now there is not so
much pain in the heart, there is so much
pain when she was crying, Payal and I were feeling so much
from inside that brother, the
pain she is feeling, the same pain is being felt
in our hearts.  But it is the same thing that we are
not able to do anything.  She was not so helpless, so powerless that she was
not
able to do anything.  I am the one who says that when children get hurt or
something happens, it is the
parents' heart that hurts the most.
Everyone asks, but
begging from parents is a different thing, guys.  So guys,
here I am teaching Zed.  He is
saying, Mom, teach me how to make a heart.
So I've put dots.  I
said, you connect the dots, I will see.
Who has such a dirty heart, yuck?
I'll go [screaming sound].   It's
not much of a dirty talk, it's not like that.
Then she is feeding you.  This does
not mean that you will move things around.  Say
sorry to her right now.
I won't do it.
Sorry to.   I will
not do it.
Say sorry now.   I will
Dirty talk, right?
Mom, I am feeling cold.   I will
stop doing this right now.
Mom, please fix my [ __ ] too.  Should I fix your [ __ ]
too?
And he is also feeling cold.
[ __ ] it, I quickly switched off the AC.   I am feeling
cold, Mom.   Turned
off the AC.
I am such a sweet momma thank you.
I love you my love.
Mom,
look at me, my daughter, listen.  Listen my daughter.   The
doctor has told you to give him medicine at 11:30.
Mom will give you medicine.  She will make you
sleep on her hands the whole night.  Ok?  She wo
n't even let you do that.  Ok?
Still feeling cold.   Should I turn
off the fan?  Yes, this is wrong.  So guys, it's
10:00 pm now brother.  At 11:30
I have to give medicine to Na Tuba.  So
I sent Zad into the room.  I have
told Chiku to sleep because this boy has been awake since morning.
So I said he has
not slept yet.  Chiku, go to sleep.  You know guys,
children feel that they don't know what their parents are
saying.  If someone tells me to
sleep, I will fall asleep in a second.
Payal did not sleep even in the afternoon.  Mom is
saying, Mom, let me go for a walk in the morning.
Subu, how long do you want to visit mom?  Yes,
very late.  [laughs]
So she's hanging out with me this afternoon, so
my duty has just begun.  I will keep going
from here to here.  Are you okay
Tuba?
Yes sir.
So Tuba has taken Guy's medicine.  Just now, Tuba,
tell me one thing, daughter.  The way you are
placing your hand, it will hurt you a lot.  Should
I take care of you well?
No, mom.
You have to wait wait wait wait wait.
Mama.
You put your hand on this.  Put it on this.  Keep it on this.
Yes.  Keep it easy.  How are you feeling now
?   It's
very good.
Feeling good, right?  Your hand will hurt,
son.  You will keep it in the air.  Nothing will happen to you.
Papa has got the bandage done, right mom and
dad?  Nothing will happen to you now.  Ok?
Mom, what is this?
What son?
What is this?
This is a bandage.  Is there tape?  Guys,
I can't find this kid.  If someone
finds it somewhere, please tell me where it is?  She has wandered somewhere.
Mom, I am not roaming around, I am here.
Where is that girl?   It is
here.   It is
raining so nicely here.
Now my hair has also grown long.
So how did your hair grow long?  You
are just small inside it.   You
are small, right?
Yes.  Are you taller now?
Yes.
You apply oil, right?   Yes, yes.
We know this is your secret.  Well done, well done
my lion, well done.  All your actions are
recorded.  The thumb you drank is a
dirty thing.  Ishq does not drink.  Ishq does
not drink.  It has come son.  Ishq does not drink.
Yes, you say goodbye,
I had put the phone on charging.  Leave it
son.   Make a
cut in the scarf.
What is he saying?
What?
Put a pistol in the scarf.
Should I point the gun?  Tuba friend, he got angry with
me.
Why?   I do
n't know, ask me sister.
Oye oy [screaming sound]
[laughter]
Don't scream too much.
Tuba is not feeling well, not much.  What had
always happened to Jack?  Why?  Zd.  Zad please talk
to me.  Ok.  I am going.  Bye.  I am leaving.
I am leaving.  I wanted to play a prank on you.
Baba,
I thought you were always angry.
I had to go and prank everyone.
This was a prank.  Oh, I am convinced by your words.
Carefully, carefully, carefully, carefully,
son, Tuba will get it.  Please take
extra care of him here.
So guys brother it's already 12 o'clock at night.
So brother, just now Tuba's health is getting a little
worse, guys.  So now we are
taking him to the hospital.  He
vomited a lot at night also.  We gave
him medicine and since yesterday he has not eaten anything properly.  Isn't it
?  Didn't eat at all.  Just a
little bit more.
Come on, come on, take out the car.  Come on, come on.
This made me vomit.
Papa, I am also here,
you stay at home, I will go and come back in five minutes.
Ok?
Papa, it's okay.   Ok ok.
Golu, he will study today, right?  Today
is Sunday brother.  Are?
I was thinking about this.  I said ma'am is about to come.
Today I will teach him something good.
Golu, I have to buy some things for the children today.  So
I am thinking of taking that.
Yes son.
Today is Sunday.
Son, I know daughter, today is Sunday.
Where are you going now?   I am
wearing slippers.
Where are you going Krishna?
With whom?  So
we are with you, you stay at home, okay? No
dad, if you want to come
with me, then
brother, both the children have
worn their slippers upside down, learn to wear them straight,
throw away the slippers, they are
dirty, yes,
wow brother, wow, your
foot got cut, right, what happened just this
morning, tell me what you are
feeling, you have stomach ache,
yes, it
is severe, we are just going to the
hospital, okay, I will get you
admitted first,
okay
son, you will have to get yourself
checked, if you are seriously ill then you are vomiting, you are telling about stomach ache again and again, I am
giving you medicine
and you are not eating anything, you are not eating anything since yesterday.
Papa, there are a lot of insects in his head.
Yes
what?   There are
many insects in their body.   There are
many worms in its stomach.
How have they been?   Do
n't know.
How are you brother?   I don't know if
Guddu gets it on children, all
three will have to get dewormed.
Son, what are you playing?  You
come and meet me in the lift, three years.   Do you know how to
play?
Yes.
Show me how you are playing.
Come meet me.
Run a raw thread race.  Pluck 10 leaves, one
leaf raw.   It's
painful to eat two.
Oh my son, I will not say anything.
Daughter, eat something.  Your health will not deteriorate so much.   Your
health will improve if you eat.
He is saying that you will not feel unwell if you eat something.
Okay, okay, sorry, sorry.   Are in
love.
So brother, just now Tuba's pulse is being checked
and it is fine.
Okay doctor.  90/12
If you don't listen to me, I will give you an injection.
Won't you inject me?  Yes sir.  I will get it installed.   Will you
inject me?
Yes sir.
Why?
Why?  Are you not listening to me?
I have a little fever.
Well, don't you have fever?
No.
So should I not get the injection?
No.   I will get
one installed.
Do you have a thick brain?
What is?
What?
I have a thick brain?
Yes.   Does
anyone talk to father like this?  Who speaks
like this?   Are
you crazy?
Yes, I am crazy.  Speak now.
So tell me to get it fixed and come back.
I felt nothing.
So brother, here we are showing Tubapa to the
doctor.  Doctor Sahib is asking
what happened?
Where does it happen?  Tell me by touching it.  Here,
yes, yes
brother, I just got him checked by the doctor. The
doctor has prescribed medicines and also
said, brother, feed him something. Whatever has happened to him since yesterday, it is
very important to feed him, if you don't feed him, he will feel weak.
Tuba, yes,
you have to eat now, daughter. Okay, yes, okay, if you don't
eat, you will get
beaten. You wo
n't get beaten, you won't get sick, you will feel
weak. You are
fine, I will
eat. Doctor,
yes, good, so guys, I have just reached home.
Tuba, you promised me, will you
eat food, will you eat with me?  Correct.  How many hours of
fasting?   It's about to be
17 hours.
Ok.
So it's 1:30 right now guys and at 1:30
when did he eat his fasting food?
I had dinner at 9:00 pm.
What time will I eat now?  3:00 pm.
How long will the pill fasting last for an hour?
I am
continuing one day.
So brother, here Payal also took a challenge.
365 days means a hard challenge.
365 Days Hard Challenge.
gym?
gym.
What will happen Payal?
And daily routine what I am eating and drinking.
Whatever I am using on my face,
for my body, food I am eating
, 4 litres of water a day, I should show all that.
Why are you angry?
You have to go to Haridwar.   I have to
go to Haridwar.  It is the month of Sawan.
Tuba will be fine, right?  I will take you along with Tuba.
Ok.
Tuba, you are so fine.
Why are you not eating food?
Father.   It is
coming.  It is coming.  Coming in the second lift.
In the second lift.   It has
not fallen.  Well,
coming in the second lift.  Where are you coming from?
Ok?  So brother, many people post our
videos, photos and I don't know what else
on social media and earn money.
So brother, bring your own content.  Right now, you can say that we have
destroyed 50 to 60 channels by giving strike.  Because brother,
our things are getting spoiled.  You guys should
do something about it by fasting and doing things.
If anyone uploads my video, brother, I will
blow up the channel immediately.  You are
not my relative.  Do it yourself.  And many
people are threatening Deepak that brother
why did you strike our channel?  This is
him.  So brother, do whatever you can.